MICHALIS MAVROMATAKIS

Senior Full-Stack Developer

- michamav19@gmail.com
- **J** 0030 6959783619
- Athens
 - https://www.linkedin.com/in/micha lis-mavromatakis

SKILLS

- JavaScript, Typescript, jQuery
- React|S, Next|s
- NodeJS, ExpressJS, PHP, Java
- MySQL, NoSQL
- · Github, Docker
- AWS, MongoDB, Postgres DB
- Figma, WordPress
- · Windows, MacOS, Linux, Office

EDUCATION

Bachelor's Degree

Department of Management Science And Technology, **AUEB**

- 2013-09 2018-04
- Athens
- Grade: 7.1/10

Relevant courses

- Major in E-Commerce, Innovation and Entrepreneurship, Grade: 7.5/10
- Minor in Information Systems and Technologies, Grade: 8.2/10

Web Design And Front End Developer Expertise

Web Development E-learning, UOA

- 2019-10 2020-03
- Athens
- Grade: 9.4/10

Varvakeio School

- **==** 2007-09 2013-06
- Athens

SUMMARY

Experienced Senior Full Stack Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the software engineer with knowledge of complete product lifecycle through requirements, analysis, data modeling, design, development, testing, documentation and delivery of projects. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Department of Management Science and Technology from Athens University of Economics and Business.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior Full-Stack Engineer, FlexCar

- 🚞 2022-09 current
- Athens
- Develop and implement an app for history-live tracking, geofencing alerts, installation process dashboard for sims and trackers, cron-jobs for getting data from 3rd party apps via API calls for sims and trackers info and save them to our DB
- Develop and implement an app for colleagues to upload files and data of customers to our DB and S3 Bucket.
- Weekly meetings with product team members for new tasks
- Tech design of new tasks and delegate them to team members
- Daily code reviews and QA of team members' tasks
- Technologies: ReactJs, NextJs, TypeScript, NodeJs, ExpressJS | MongoDB, Postgres DB, AWS (TimeStream, S3) | ECR, ECS, Fargate, Amplify, CloudWatch, API Gateway, Docker | Github, CI-CD workflows

Lead Full-Stack Engineer, Collegelink

- **=== 2021-06 2022-08**
- Athens
- Design and implement full-stack projects
- Check team members' task progress with agile project management method
- Delegate work and assignments to team members
- Weekly meetings with team members for career roadmaps to improve hard & soft skills
- Weekly code reviews and QA to team members' tasks
- Git & Auto Deployment roadmaps implementations
- · Write onboarding and technical documentations

Full-Stack Developer, KEPYES/GES

- **=== 2020-10 2021-06**
- Athens
- Front-End: HTML, CSS, SCSS, React|s
- Back-end: PHP Symfony
- DataBase: Oracle DB, SQL
- Programs: Visual Studio Code, WebStorm, PhpStorm, DataGrip
- Other: GitLab, Linux

Full-Stack Developer, Collegelink

- **=== 2018-03 2020-09**
- Athens
- Front-End: HTML, CSS, Javascript, jQuery, AJAX
- · Back-end: PHP
- DataBase: Workbench, SQL
- · Project management tool: Jira
- · Other: GitKraken, MacOS, Windows, Visual Studio Code, Figma